<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PwzXxm</title>
    <description>Learning and sharing computer science ideas. Enjoy what you are passionated about.</description>
    <link>http://pwzxxm.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://pwzxxm.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 19:47:56 +1100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 19:47:56 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Story About the Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pwzxxm.com&quot;&gt;PwzXxm&lt;/a&gt; is my first blog and also my first website I have ever built. I knew only a little bit of HTML before I started this project. I learned CSS and JavaScript while I&amp;#39;m building the site. I also read a lot of source code and blog posts about how other people build their own site using &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. It took me seven days. Finally, on the 10th of December, 2015, the site went alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Details about building the site. (click me) (not yet, still editing)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was learning algorithms, c++ and practice ACM-ICPC but I stuck at graph theory and I did not have any progress on one particular problem for like three or four days. I always want to build a website and start writing some stuff. So I put other things aside and started to build this blog, and my friends give a lot of suggestions on the design of the website. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two reasons why I really want to start this blog. One is that blogging helps me clear my thoughts. For instance, if you can teach an algorithm to a man which is new to him and he can understand the algorithm very well as your explanation is clear, you should also already have a deep understanding on this algorithm. So another reason is that I&amp;#39;m hoping someone can learn something from my blog. There a story: one day, I was trying to learn KMP (a string search algorithm), I barely understand it. I read a lot of posts from other people&amp;#39;s blog, watched youtube videos and tried to do it on a paper. Suddenly, I knew the ideas behind it. Thanks for the guys sharing their ideas and thinkings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anyone find any mistake on my blog, please feel free to contact me or leave a comment below the post. Contact details are shown on the footer on every pages of the blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s learn together and sharing ideas!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>http://pwzxxm.com/the-story-about-the-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://pwzxxm.com/the-story-about-the-blog/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>这个博客那些事</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pwzxxm.com/cn/index.html&quot;&gt;PwzXxm&lt;/a&gt;是我的第一个网站，也是第一个博客。一开始只知道一点点基本的HTML，后来一边学CSS，JavaScript，用&lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;东拼西凑，花了7天时间，在2015年12月10日终于把它基本上都写完了。写完的时候真是感觉能内裤外穿一垛冲天。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;关于建站的详细过程（点我）(还在编辑中).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;原来我是在看算法，刷题做ACM和看C++的，后来看着看着卡住了，想了几天也没什么头绪。我一直想着想做个网站写点东西，就先留着坑，跑来开了这个新坑。在写的过程中，好多朋友给了设计上的建议，谢谢他们～（鞠躬）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;开这个博客，一个是想自己理理思路，想算法啊什么的如果能说得新手明白，那自己也应该理解得差不多了；还有就是希望别人看了这个博客能有所收获吧。因为很久以前看KMP（一个字符串匹配算法）的时候，刚开始真的是云里雾里，智商不够。后来看了好多别人写的文章，突然有一瞬间看着看着就觉得自己好像会了。谢谢那些无私写作发到博客里的大牛们，如果大牛们看见有哪写的不对的也希望能及时联系我，避免误人子弟。联系方式在每页的页脚都有显示。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;看我发功！
哼————哈！
大家一起加油！！！&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>http://pwzxxm.com/cn/the-story-about-the-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://pwzxxm.com/cn/the-story-about-the-blog/</guid>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the site. Love you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>http://pwzxxm.com/welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://pwzxxm.com/welcome/</guid>
        
        <category>welcome</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>欢迎</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;欢迎光临～ 么么哒～&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>http://pwzxxm.com/cn/welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://pwzxxm.com/cn/welcome/</guid>
        
        <category>welcome</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
