<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>POJ - Tag - PwzXxm</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/tags/poj/</link><description>POJ - Tag - PwzXxm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>patrick.weizhixu@hotmail.com (PwzXxm)</managingEditor><webMaster>patrick.weizhixu@hotmail.com (PwzXxm)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pwzxxm.com/tags/poj/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>POJ 3279 Fliptile</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3279/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3279/</guid><description>There are \(M \times N\) \((1 \le M, N \le 15)\)square tiles. Each tile can be flipped and the color of tile can change between black(1) and white(0).
When you flip a tile, 4 adjacent tiles will also be flipped. Note that the four adjacent flipped tiles will NOT cause their adjacent tiles to flip.
Given a configuration, find the minimum number of flips so that all square tiles become white.</description></item><item><title>POJ 3268 Silver Cow Party</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3268/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3268/</guid><description>There are one cow from each \(N\) (\(1 \le N \le 1000\)) farms want to go to the number X farm to have a party, hurrah! One cow from each farm need to go to the party and go back. There are \(M\) (\(1 \le M \le 100,000\)) weighted (represents time) one-direction roads connects pairs of roads. Cows are smart though, they want to go via the shortest path. The question is, what is the longest time the cow will take.</description></item><item><title>POJ 2376 Cleaning Shifts</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-2376/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-2376/</guid><description>\(N\) (\(1 \le N \le 25,000\)) cows, each cow only available for a interval of time. \(T\) (\(1 \le T \le 1,000,000\)) shifts. Find minimum number of cows to complete \(T\) shifts.
Link: http://poj.org/problem?id=2376
Notes Each shift must has at least one cow assigned to it. A cow finishes after the end time. That is, if there are two cows, start and end at \((1, 3)\) and \((4, 10)\) respectively.</description></item><item><title>POJ 3050 Hopscotch</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 22:22:00 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3050/</guid><description>There is a 5 * 5 array filled with integers. You can only go up, down, left and right. You can start on any point in the array and can only move 5 times. Therefore, you will get 6 integers.
Find the number of distinct integers you can constructed.
Link: http://poj.org/problem?id=3050
Solution I use a set to avoid same sequences. Since there are only 6 steps and the array is only 5*5, dfs each point, add into the set.</description></item><item><title>POJ 3187 Backward Digits Sums</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/poj-3187/</guid><description>There are 1 to \(N\) digits (\(1\le N \le 10\)) in certain order. Add adjacent numbers together to get the next line, until the there is only one number left.(Just like Pascal&amp;rsquo;s triangle) For example, there are 3 integers: $$ 1, 2, 3 $$ $$ 3, 5 $$ $$ 8 $$
So, given \(N\) and the final sum, find the lexicographically least ordering of integers.
Link: http://poj.org/problem?id=3187
Notes: Be aware of that the question is asking 1 to \(N\) digits, so we don&amp;rsquo;t have to test all possible permutations from 1 to 10.</description></item></channel></rss>