<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Blog - Tag - PwzXxm</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/tags/blog/</link><description>Blog - Tag - PwzXxm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>patrick.weizhixu@hotmail.com (PwzXxm)</managingEditor><webMaster>patrick.weizhixu@hotmail.com (PwzXxm)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 14:43:36 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pwzxxm.com/tags/blog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog Renovation - From Jekyll to Hugo</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/blog-renovation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 14:43:36 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/blog-renovation/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>In the past years, the blog was generated using <a href="https://jekyllrb.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Jekyll</a>.
Recently, I decided to migrate to <a href="https://gohugo.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Hugo</a> along with other changes, such as utilising discussion plugin <a href="https://valine.js.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Valine</a>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Using Jekyll + Github Pages to build a blog</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/building-blog-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/building-blog-jekyll/</guid><description>Why Jekyll and Github Pages Jekyll is an static site generator, it is simple to use with YAML front matter. It is quite convenient to blog with markdown and Jekyll supports it build-in. Github Pages provide the space to host the website for free. Both of them are well-documented, and works well with each other. One thing that makes they works well but not perfect is that although Github Pages can generate the website using Jekyll but as it generates in safe mode, it does not support Jekyll plugin.</description></item><item><title>The Story About the Blog</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/the-story-about-the-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/the-story-about-the-blog/</guid><description>PwzXxm is my first blog and also my first website I have ever built. I knew only a little bit of HTML before I started this project. I learned CSS and JavaScript while I&amp;rsquo;m building the site. I also read a lot of source code and blog posts about how other people build their own site using Jekyll. It took me seven days. Finally, on the 10th of December, 2015, the site went alive.</description></item></channel></rss>