<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Practice - Tag - PwzXxm</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/tags/practice/</link><description>Practice - Tag - PwzXxm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>patrick.weizhixu@hotmail.com (PwzXxm)</managingEditor><webMaster>patrick.weizhixu@hotmail.com (PwzXxm)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 15:39:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pwzxxm.com/tags/practice/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build a Proxy Server to Access Chinese IP Including Netease Music</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/proxy-server-cn-netease-music/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 15:39:00 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/proxy-server-cn-netease-music/</guid><description>Sometimes we need to access Chinese content, like Youku Video, Netease Music (Cloud Music) and QQ music. It is very annoying to get &amp;ldquo;Can Only Be Streamed in Mainland China&amp;rdquo; or similar messages. Being tired of that, fortunately I have got a VPS from Aliyun and I build a proxy server using Shadowsocks on it and everything works smoothly now.
VPS You need to have a VPS with Chinese IP address, there are tons of choices, like Aliyun(Alibaba Cloud) and Tencent Cloud etc.</description></item><item><title>Using Jekyll + Github Pages to build a blog</title><link>https://www.pwzxxm.com/building-blog-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://www.pwzxxm.com/building-blog-jekyll/</guid><description>Why Jekyll and Github Pages Jekyll is an static site generator, it is simple to use with YAML front matter. It is quite convenient to blog with markdown and Jekyll supports it build-in. Github Pages provide the space to host the website for free. Both of them are well-documented, and works well with each other. One thing that makes they works well but not perfect is that although Github Pages can generate the website using Jekyll but as it generates in safe mode, it does not support Jekyll plugin.</description></item></channel></rss>